<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<Movie>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5149</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/haunted.gif</picture>
<movie_title>(2D) A HAUNTED HOUSE</movie_title>
<synopsis>In an outrageous send up of the Paranormal Activity movies, The Devil Inside and other "found footage" movies, A HAUNTED HOUSE features young couple Malcolm and Kisha who have just moved in to their dream house. As they settle in, they quickly find they're not alone. But it's not the house that's haunted, it's Malcolm's girlfriend who is possessed by a demon. Malcolm hires everyone from a priest to modern day ghostbusters to rid her of this unwelcome intruder, determined not to let the evil spirit ruin his relationship... or, more importantly, his sex life.</synopsis>
<cast>Marlon Wayans, Essence Atkins, Cedric the Entertainer, Nick Swardson</cast>
<tentative>1/16/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5148</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/miserables.gif</picture>
<movie_title>(2D) LES MISERABLES</movie_title>
<synopsis>Les Misérables tells an enthralling story of broken dreams and unrequited love, passion, sacrifice and redemption-a timeless testament to the survival of the human spirit. Jackman plays ex-prisoner Jean Valjean, hunted for decades by the ruthless policeman Javert (Crowe) after he breaks parole. When Valjean agrees to care for factory worker Fantine's (Hathaway) young daughter, Cosette, their lives change forever. In December 2012, the world's longest-running musical brings its power to the big screen in Tom Hooper's sweeping and spectacular interpretation of Victor Hugo's epic tale.</synopsis>
<cast>Anne Hathaway, Hugh Jackman, Russell Crowe, Amanda Seyfried </cast>
<tentative>1/16/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5141</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/haunted.gif</picture>
<movie_title>A HAUNTED HOUSE</movie_title>
<synopsis>In an outrageous send up of the Paranormal Activity movies, The Devil Inside and other "found footage" movies, A HAUNTED HOUSE features young couple Malcolm and Kisha who have just moved in to their dream house. As they settle in, they quickly find they're not alone. But it's not the house that's haunted, it's Malcolm's girlfriend who is possessed by a demon. Malcolm hires everyone from a priest to modern day ghostbusters to rid her of this unwelcome intruder, determined not to let the evil spirit ruin his relationship... or, more importantly, his sex life.</synopsis>
<cast>Marlon Wayans, Essence Atkins, Cedric the Entertainer, Nick Swardson</cast>
<tentative>1/16/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5145</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/brokencity.gif</picture>
<movie_title>BROKEN CITY</movie_title>
<synopsis>An ex-cop-turned-private eye (Mark Wahlberg) is thrown headfirst into a hotbed of trouble after a mayor (Russell Crowe) hires him to look into his cheating wife. Book of Eli's Allen Hughes directs from a script by Brian Tucker.</synopsis>
<cast>Mark Wahlberg, Russell Crowe, Catherine Zeta-Jones</cast>
<tentative>2/6/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5146</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/bullet.gif</picture>
<movie_title>BULLET TO THE HEAD</movie_title>
<synopsis>Based on a graphic novel, Bullet to the Head tells the story of a New Orleans hitman (Stallone) and a DC cop (Kang) who form an alliance to bring down the killers of their respective partners.</synopsis>
<cast>Sylvester Stallone, Sung Kang, Sarah Shahi</cast>
<tentative>2/6/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5144</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/zodiac.gif</picture>
<movie_title>CHINESE ZODIAC</movie_title>
<synopsis>A man searches the world for a set of mystic artifacts - 12 bronze heads of the animals from the Chinese zodiac.</synopsis>
<cast>Jackie Chan, Oliver Platt</cast>
<tentative>1/30/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5056</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/django.gif</picture>
<movie_title>DJANGO UNCHAINED</movie_title>
<synopsis>Django, a slave whose brutal history with his former owners lands him face-to-face with German-born bounty hunter Dr. King Schultz. Schultz is on the trail of the murderous Brittle brothers, and only Django can lead him to his bounty. Honing vital hunting skills, Django remains focused on one goal: finding and rescuing Broomhilda the wife he lost to the slave trade long ago. Django and Schultz's search ultimately leads them to Calvin Candie the proprietor of "Candyland," an infamous plantation.</synopsis>
<cast>Jamie Foxx, Leonardo De Caprio, Christoph Waltz, Samuel L. Jackson</cast>
<tentative>4/10/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5131</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/miserables.gif</picture>
<movie_title>LES MISERABLES</movie_title>
<synopsis>Les Misérables tells an enthralling story of broken dreams and unrequited love, passion, sacrifice and redemption-a timeless testament to the survival of the human spirit. Jackman plays ex-prisoner Jean Valjean, hunted for decades by the ruthless policeman Javert (Crowe) after he breaks parole. When Valjean agrees to care for factory worker Fantine's (Hathaway) young daughter, Cosette, their lives change forever. In December 2012, the world's longest-running musical brings its power to the big screen in Tom Hooper's sweeping and spectacular interpretation of Victor Hugo's epic tale.</synopsis>
<cast>Anne Hathaway, Hugh Jackman, Russell Crowe, Amanda Seyfried </cast>
<tentative>1/16/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5142</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/pg.gif</picture>
<movie_title>PARENTAL GUIDANCE</movie_title>
<synopsis>Old school grandfather Artie (Billy Crystal), who is accustomed to calling the shots, meets his match when he and his eager-to-please wife Diane (Bette Midler) agree to babysit their three grandkids when their type-A helicopter parents (Marisa Tomei, Tom Everett Scott) go away for work. But when 21st century problems collide with Artie and Diane's old school methods of tough rules, lots of love and old-fashioned games, it's learning to bend - and not holding your ground - that binds a family together.</synopsis>
<cast>Billy Crystal, Bette Midler, Marisa Tomei, Tom Everett Scott</cast>
<tentative>1/16/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5132</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/parker.gif</picture>
<movie_title>PARKER</movie_title>
<synopsis>Parker is a professional thief who lives by a personal code of ethics: Don&#8217;t steal from people who can&#8217;t afford it and don&#8217;t hurt people who don&#8217;t deserve it. But on his latest heist, his crew double crosses him, steals his stash, and leaves him for dead. Determined to make sure they regret it, Parker tracks them to PalmBeach, playground of the rich and famous. Donning the disguise of a rich Texan, Parker takes on an unlikely partner, Leslie, a savvy insider. Together, they devise a plan to hijack the score, take everyone down and get away clean.</synopsis>
<cast>Jason Statham, Jennifer Lopez, Clifton Collins Jr.,</cast>
<tentative>1/24/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5143</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/laststand.gif</picture>
<movie_title>THE LAST STAND</movie_title>
<synopsis>Sheriff Owens is a man who has resigned himself to a life of fighting what little crime takes place in sleepy border town Sommerton Junction after leaving his LAPD post following a bungled operation that left him wracked with failure and defeat after his partner was crippled. After a spectacular escape from an FBI prisoner convoy, the most notorious, wanted drug kingpin in the hemisphere is hurtling toward the border at 200 mph in a specially outfitted car with a hostage and a fierce army of gang members.</synopsis>
<cast>Arnold Schwarzenegger, Peter Stormare, Forest Whitaker, Jaimie Alexander</cast>
<tentative>1/16/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
<Coming_Soon>
<id>5053</id>
<picture>http://www.sureseats.com/images/events/movies/thumbnails/smurfs.gif</picture>
<movie_title>THE SMURFS 2</movie_title>
<synopsis>The Smurfs team up with their human friends to rescue Smurfette, who has been kidnapped by Gargamel since she knows a secret spell that can turn the evil sorcerer's newest creation - creatures called the Naughties - into real Smurfs.</synopsis>
<cast>Hank Azaria, Christina Ricci, J.B. Smoove</cast>
<tentative>8/14/2013</tentative>
</Coming_Soon>
</Movie>